

# MARÍA ALEJANDRA **GAITÁN ALFÉREZ**

**FULLSTACK JR** UI | UX DESIGNER - JR.



### PERSONAL DETAILS

- Bogotá Colombia
- (312) 339 . 66 . 83
- ✓ maleja8005@gmail.com
- /alejandra\_bf2a
- in/malejandragaitana/
- github.com/Maga8005

### **ABOUT ME**

Web Developer jr, with knowledge in UX/UI design and experience as a graphic and packaging designer. Having as goal to facilitate the user experience, mainly in the product development process. Wanting to consolidate and expand my digital skills, and contribute to different web projects.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Fullstack Developer

**DIGITAL HOUSE** 



Project: TempoBuono.com | E-commerce January 2022 - July 2022



 User interface design. Web layout. Frontend and Backend development. CRUD. Forms validation (Front|Back). Database integration. API's injection.

# UX|UI Designer

Google UX Design Certificate Coursera

Project: Tropical Snack Bit App July 2021 - December 2021 - 3 Levels



- Foundations of User Experience Design.
- UX Design Process: Empathize, Define and Ideate.
- Build wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes.

# Web Designer

**Multimedia Applications Master** Universitat Oberta of Catalunya

Project: SexoDCero January 2019 - July 2019



UI, Frontend development, API's consumption, web analytics and performance, and SEO.

### OTHER EXPERIENCES

- Creative & packaging Designer 2017 - Currently
- Graphic Designer 2013 - 2016

**Colprinter SAS** Senior Designer

**Colprinter SAS** 3D Designer

### **EDUCATION**



FullStack Developer Digital House | 2022



Multimedia Applications Master U. Oberta de Catalunya | 2017 - 19 ICETEX scholarship holder



Illustration Specialist SENA. Cenigraf | 2016



3D Animation Technologist SENA. Cenigraf | 2012 - 14



Industrial Designt U. Nacional de Colombia | 2002 - 07



Graphic Design 4 Sem U. Jorge Tadeo Lozano | 1998

### **COURSES AND** CERTIFICATIONS

- User Experience: The Beginner's Guide Interaction Design Foundation | 2021
- Learn Figma: UI Design Essentials Udemy | 2020

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML CSS
- MVC
- JavaScript
- React
- Express
- Boostrap
- Node JS
- Consumo APIs
- VS Code
- Figma
- Git GitHub
- **UX** Research
- MSQL
- Low Prototypes

#### LANGUAGES



→ English B1